what's up guys today we're going to be
making a lotus biscoff
cheesecake first up you need crushed
lotus biscuits
then add your melted butter and mix
these together
pop this into a cake tin pressing it
down to form your base
set this aside now add your cream cheese
caster sugar and vanilla extract to a
bowl
and whisk these together then add three
quarters of your biscoff spread and beat
until smooth
pour in your double cream and whisk for
a few minutes then stir in the rest of
your biscoff spread to create some
swirls
pour the cheesecake mix onto your
biscuit base spreading it out so it's
nice and smooth
pop it in the fridge for six hours or
overnight if possible
to decorate melt some biscoff's bread
and pour onto the cheesecake
spread it out gently and keep adding
more until it's completely covered and
smooth
we also added a drip around the edges
add some crumbled lotus biscuits around
the edge and finish it off with a
biscuit
and we're done enjoy